you're listening to a toadstool in fairness production of green eggs and ham by Dr Seuss
be sure to hit the thumbs-up button and subscribe it lets you to know that you're
interested in more videos like this
I am Sam
Sam I am
that Sam I am that Sam I am I do not like that Sam I am
do you like green eggs and hale
I do not like them Sam I am I do not like green eggs and ham
would you like them here or there
I would not like them here or there I would not like them anywhere I do
not like green eggs and ham I do not like them Sam I am
would you like them in a house would you like them with the mouse
I do not like them in a house and I do not like them with a
mouse I do not like them here or there I do not like them anywhere
I do not like green eggs and ham I do not like them Sam I am
would you eat them in a box who would you eat them with a fox
not in a box not with a fox not in a house not with a mouse
I would not eat them here or there I would not eat them anywhere I would
not eat green eggs and ham I do not like them Sam I am
would you could you in a car eat them eat them here they are
I would not could not in a car
you may like them you will see you may like them in a tree
I would not could not in a tree not in a car you let me be
I do not like them in a box I do not like them with a fox
I do not like them in a house and I do not like them the mouth
I do not like them here or there I do not like them anywhere I do
not like green eggs and ham I do not like them Sam I am
a train a true a train a train could you would you on a train
not on a train not in a tree not in a car Sam let me be
I would not could not in a box I could not would not with a box
I will not eat them with a mouse I will not eat them in a house
I will not eat them here or there I will not eat them anywhere I do
not like green eggs and ham I do not like them Sam I am
would you could you in the rain
I would not could not in the rain not in the dark not on a train
not in a car not in a tree I do not like them Sam you see
not in a house not in a box not with a mouse not with a fox
I will not eat them here or there I do not like them anywhere
you do not like green eggs and
I do not like them Sam I am
could you would you with a goat
I would not could not with a goat
would you could you on a boat
I could not would not on a boat I will not will not with a goat
I will not eat them in the rain I will not eat them on a train
not in the dark not in a tree not in a car now you let me
be I do not like them in a box I do not like them with a
fox I will not eat them in a house I do not like them with a
mouse I do not like them here or there I do not like them where
I do not like green eggs and ham
I do not like them damn
you do not like them so you say try them try them and you may try
them and you may I say
Sam
if you will let me be
I will try them you will see
I like green a gun ham to I like them Sam I am and I would
eat them in a boat
and I would eat them with a gun
and I would eat them in the rain and in the dark it on a train
and in a car and in a tree
they are so good so good you see
so I will eat them in a box and I believe them with the pot and
I will leave them in a house and I won't eat them with a mouse and
I will leave them here and there say I will leave them anywhere
I do so like green eggs and ham thank you thank you Sam I am