everybody knows that you only sandwood with the grain but is everybody wrong the answer is
kind of yeah only standing wood with the grain is sort of a holdover from the
old days when we had a handstand everything and in the case of hand standing yes
you only want to go with the grain either with just that she to sandpaper or
with something like these standing blocks like we've all probably used however just like everything else
in the world there's been advancements in technology and now most of us have something called
a random orbital sander if you think about how a random orbital sander works it will
make sense pretty quick why you don't necessarily need to go with the grain a random
orbell center will vibrate in random directions it will also spin the entire time you operate
it meaning that even if you're going with the grain that spinning action is actually hitting
the grain from every possible direction including with it across at diagonal every possible direction so
you don't necessarily need to go with the grain in fact I try to mix up
my standing pattern going with it across it diagonal and really just mixing at my pattern
altogether